Characters, actions, places, occupations, and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
(Did you know)
(that Halley’s Comet)
(has an orbital period of about 76 years?)
(I’ve never seen it.)
(I wasn’t born yet.)
(But someone told me that)
(in 30-plus years,)
(it’ll return.)
(I haven’t seen all my friends together
in almost three years.)
(Thara is a lawyer now.)
Why do you keep spinning it?
- Well, otherwise, you'll eat it all.
- (Pok has his own songs.)
Oh, come on.
(As for Hem…)
Do you guys think
- (He’s gone off the rails.)
- I should dye my hair blond?
You’ve been saying
you’d dye your hair blond
since we were in school.
I still haven’t seen you do it.
Can you guys stop arguing already?
My friend Cheewa is here.
(And that’s Parncheewa.)
(He’s the one who said)
It’s gravity.
(the comet)
(will return in 35 years.)
You really like these old songbooks, huh?
No one uses them anymore, dude.
Do you think I should dye my hair blond?
I’d look so cool playing guitar.
Hmm…
Before you get to be cool,
you’ll be making a trip to the discipline office.
Suchart won’t let you graduate.
What the hell?
Why does the school have to get in the way
of my journey as a musician?
Don’t they want a cool guitarist
as an alumnus?
Oh.
What’s going on here?
Is he hibernating or something?
Seriously.
You have your own club to sleep in.
This is the Music Club.
Why are you sleeping here?
Yeah,
Thara is going to think
we locked you up again.
We’re good-looking musicians.
We’re tiny.
How could we lock athletes
like you guys up?
Mm.
You’re giants.
If you threw us, we'd break our bones.
What’s wrong?
Why’s your face all scrunched up like that?
What are you upset about?
Did you fight with your dad?
Have you been busy with school?
Same as usual.
Coach Ong called me yesterday.
He said you missed practice.
I had a headache,
so I went to rest in the nurse’s office.
You looked fine
when you came home yesterday.
How did you have a headache?
You need to be more responsible.
Go to practice regularly.
You’re a grown-up now.
I don’t want to keep nagging you.
Okay.
You guys seriously want to be musicians?
I see you guys practicing every day.
Come on.
What kind of question is that?
Of course we do.
We only have one dream.
Just you wait.
Once I graduate, I’m going to put out a tape
that’ll be playing everywhere.
Yeah.
I’m going to put out a tape as a real artist.
Corporate jobs
aren’t our thing.
Just so you know,
no one makes tapes anymore, Mr. Hemaraj.
Well, I like them.
Oh.
We still have a few years
before we graduate.
How did you guys figure yourselves out
so fast?
I don’t know if I’ll really become a singer
in the future,
but it’s what I like now, so I keep practicing.
Just like you practice judo.
Isn’t it because you like it?
(Like it?)
(I don’t even know if I really like it.)
He’s hibernating again.
(My life is just like a dark universe.)
(Pitch black.)
(I don’t even know what I like or don’t like.)
(I just live)
(day by day.)
(So ordinary.)
(When it comes to judo,)
(it feels ordinary too.)
(No feeling.)
(No excitement.)
(I’m just Niran.)
(Nothing special.)
(That’s why I love coming here.)
(Lying down, listening to the music playing
as they chase their dreams.)
(One day, I’ll probably find my own path.)
Mr. Judo.
I knew you’d be here.
Again.
(Ugh, the judo guy is asking for me.)
Coach asked me to come get you.
Ugh!
Let’s go.
Help me.
I had nothing to do with it.
I didn’t lock him up.
I didn’t ask him to come here.
Bye-bye.
What did I tell you?
If you have a problem, come and tell me.
Don’t disappear like that.
I’m sorry, Coach.
I forgot the time.
Why didn’t you remind your friend, Thara?
Oh?
Making the national team
doesn’t mean you can skip practice, Niran.
No matter how good you are,
you still have to put in the work
and be responsible.
Otherwise, everything you’ve achieved
will slowly fade away.
Come on, Coach.
Niran is so talented.
He could keep throwing for the rest of his life.
Athletes lose because they think that way.
Oh.
I’m warning you
because I mean well.
If you really have any problems,
we can talk about them.
Got it, Niran?
Yes, Coach.
Coach must be mad at me.
For skipping practice or losing to Most?
Both.
Coach Ong can never be mad at you.
He loves you so much.
But what’s going on?
Why did you let Most throw you like that?
Did he cheat?
Do you want me to tell Coach?
Most is just really good.
Better than you?
That’s impossible.
It’s possible.
Everyone is better than me.
Except you.
You brat!
I know how to box.
Really?
Is that how you stand?
I don’t think so.
Be for real.
I’m going to punch you for real.
Oh!
Don’t run.
You can’t punch me.
Where are you going?
I’m going home.
See you, buddy.
Get home safe.
You can try to punch me tomorrow.
Bye-bye.
Yeah. See you!
Someone from the Boxing Club
walked to the basement of
the science building at night.
Then something dropped on him.
It looked just like blood.
What does that mean?
Are you insulting us, four-eyes?
Are you trying to get on my damn nerves?
Oh.
Sorry.
I lost my balance.
It’s gravity.
Huh?
You fell just now
because of gravity.
According to Newton’s law
of universal gravitation,
no matter where you are in the universe,
there’s always a gravitational pull on mass.
The force is proportional
to the product of the masses
and inversely proportional
to the square of the distance between them.
Like right now,
your gravitational force is pressing down
on my books.
Oh.
Sorry.
I didn’t mean it.
COMPLETE SUMMARY OF
HIGH SCHOOL PHYSICS
It’s alright. Gravity is normal.
Ah…
Okay.
Without gravity,
we’d all die.
Ah…
Okay.
Do you want to sit down?
Did you know there’ll be a bigger jolt
at the intersection up ahead?
What’s that?
It’s—
It's a jolt.
We just went through one.
You’re safe now.
♪ Wanna be loved ♪
No, Thipok.
You sang that line wrong.
I sang it right. It’s about the feel.
I improvised.
Ad-lib, you know?
Ad-lib.
If you don’t remember the lyrics,
you can just sing gibberish for now.
Can you really do that? Sing gibberish?
Of course.
All the famous singers do it.
If you don’t believe me, Pok will show you.
♪ Tua-tua-nga-nga, tua-tua-nga ♪
♪ Tua-nga ♪
♪ Tua-nga, tua-tua ♪
Screw gravity.
Nonsense.
Look, I’m not encouraging him to lip-sync.
He’ll memorize the lyrics tonight.
I’m sorry.
I know you love this song.
I’ll hurry home and memorize the lyrics
word for word, okay?
Or what’s got you so worked up?
Don’t tell me
you’re thinking about when you lost to Most?
Seriously?
You lost to Most?
Poor you, buddy.
This is your rock bottom.
Yeah.
That means forgetting the lyrics
isn’t a big deal.
You idiot.
It’s a big deal. Don’t be funny.
It’s just a minor slip-up, not rock bottom.
Right, Niran?
I ran all the way here.
Can you guys stop talking about judo?
You guys keep talking about it.
Damn.
What now?
By the way, guys,
have you heard about the ghost
in the science building?
Oh, I think that’s interesting.
I’m sick of hearing about judo too.
Yeah.
Go on.
Well…
They say there's a ghost roaming around
the science building lately.
How?
Someone from the Boxing Club
walked to the basement of
the science building at night.
Then something dropped on him.
It looked just like blood.
Blood?
That must be an exaggeration.
Nonsense.
Why would a ghost be in
the science building?
Why isn’t it at the Thai dance room?
But I think ghosts are everywhere, no?
Does that mean
there’s a ghost in this room?
Watch out in your judo practice room
when you two shower late at night.
What did I just tell you?
I didn’t mean it.
It’s Thara’s fault.
He provoked me.
Yeah, whatever.
I don’t know what ghost it is.
Maybe Sir Isaac Newton’s ghost.
If you guys don’t believe me,
let’s prove it together
Where’s your ghost?
Look, there’s a whole bunch of us here.
If I were that ghost, I’d be scared.
Especially with Niran here.
The ghost must be scared of
getting thrown to the ground.
Want me to throw you?
Hey, look.
Astronomy Club.
It’s on the top floor.
They say
the higher, the weirder.
This building is like that.
I think you’re the weird one.
Excuse me?
See you guys later.
Do your best at practice.
Good luck.
Don’t lose to Most again.
I don’t like his face.
Most’s face?
Your face.
You two just go.
- See you.
Bye.
You go to practice.
I’m skipping.
What?
You’re skipping again?
Why?
I’m lazy.
You should go.
Just go.
I’m gonna hurry home.
See you.
I really am out of money.
I spent all my allowance on stuff for the club.
How am I supposed to know?
You’re supposed to know
you have to pay for our dinner.
Can’t you even manage your money?
I’m sorry.
No way he’s spent it all. He’s lying.
I’m telling the truth.
Lying to you guys in this situation
would only make things worse for me.
What does that mean?
Are you insulting us, four-eyes?
No.
I’m just judging the probability
based on your personalities.
If you two change your personalities,
I’ll analyze it differently.
Are you trying to get on my damn nerves?
How is this all you have?
Naw, search him.
If there’s more, I’ll take it all.
Hey.
Do people still shake kids down
for money these days?
How much do you want?
I’ll donate it to you.
What the hell does someone from
the Judo Club like you have to do with this?
And does someone from the Boxing Club
like you not have money to eat?
Is that why you have to take it
from someone else?
Go ask your mom for it.
Are you trying to get on my nerves?
How about I kick your ass first?
Wait.
Hey…
Gravity Junior.
Run.
Hey.
I think they went that way.
Come on.
Idiots.
Blind as hell.
Niran!
Wake up, man.
Those two already left.
Are you sleeping for the world championship
or what?
Come on.
Let’s go, man.
I’m hungry.
Ugh!
You’re never awake during brainy classes.
Hi, Auntie Tang.
Hi, Niran.
Your dad told me
you don’t really finish your breakfast.
I don’t really have an appetite in the morning.
I wake up late too.
So I figured I’d just get lunch from you.
You can try other places too.
I know we’re relatives,
but you don’t have to keep eating my food.
I’m not eating it because we’re relatives,
but because it’s good.
Your food tastes comforting.
It feels like home.
Today, can I get
stir-fried vegetables and…
clear soup?
Let’s get you some meat.
Fried chicken?
Can I also get this, this, this,
and the chicken curry too?
Sure.
Hem!
Go get in line properly.
Come on.
I have you get food for me every day.
This time, I just ordered it myself.
Someone could yell at us!
I won’t.
See?
This kid is so generous.
What’s your name?
I’ll remember it.
Next time you want to order,
just ask me to do it for you.
You’re…
Parncheeaa.
It’s Parncheewa.
Parncheewa.
Right.
Cute with glasses.
My dear little brother.
Please give me a big portion.
I’m hungry.
Sure.
You’re really not mad?
No, I’m not.
You saved me yesterday.
I’m not going to get mad over
something this small.
Your food is ready.
Here you go. Extra portion for you.
Thank you, Auntie Tang.
Hem, grab me a spoon and fork.
Ugh!
The usual, please.
Alright.
Oh?
I thought you said you were getting noodles.
I walked past Niran
and saw him ordering from Auntie Tang.
It looked so good, so I went there too.
I bet you cut the line.
Right, Niran?
Obviously.
Hey!
Watch what you say.
I already asked the kid behind us.
He was okay with it.
I don’t know if he wanted to punch me, though.
He had such a poker face,
even though he’s kind of timid.
His name is…
Parngmeena.
Parncheewa.
Yeah.
Parncheewa?
Grade 11.
Student council member?
I don’t know if he’s on the student council,
but I think he’s an 11th grader.
I think I used to see him around.
He took drum classes at my dad’s school.
He’s no joke.
But he’s kind of nerdy.
He probably doesn’t play anymore.
What a cool kid.
Hey, should we invite him to join our band?
He’s on the student council.
And he’s in Teacher Boriboon’s club.
Standout.
Extracurricular kid.
Top student.
Most importantly,
he’s freaking handsome.
In that nerdy, glasses-wearing kind of way.
You forgot this at the food stall.
Damn. He’s really handsome.
The nerdy, handsome type with glasses.
Is my friend seriously having a lollipop
before food?
What?
Did you do it?
Why did you tell Suchart?
I didn’t want you to get hurt.
Why do you keep
meddling in my business?
You call this meddling?
You know Cheewa?
Are you guys close?
That kid with the glasses?
Yo!
We’re running late today.
Have you had breakfast?
No.
I woke up late too.
Seriously?
You have someone
making you breakfast every day,
and you still couldn’t wake up in time
to eat it?
I get tired of that too.
How?
Isn’t it your dad who cooks for you?
Or your Auntie Tang?
Did you guys see the school group chat?
Someone said they saw cockroaches
at Auntie Tang’s food stall.
Everyone’s bashing her.
They said they’re not buying food
from her anymore.
Not selling much today?
I’ve only sold two today.
Lunch break is almost over.
I don’t know why no one came by.
I think my food tastes the same as always.
Was it you?
What?
Did you do it?
What’s wrong with you?
Where’s your proof?
What did I do?
The proof is all over your face.
Hey.
If you’re mad at me, take it out on me.
It’s my business.
Why did you take it out on her?
What the hell does she have to do with this?
And what did you have to do with it yesterday?
Niran.
Don’t. It’s not worth it.
You should listen to your friend.
You’re only as tall as my friend’s knee.
His knee, my ass!
You jerk!
Stay the f*ck out of this!
Hey!
Stop it right now!
What were you thinking?
Fighting in the canteen?
If Cheewa hadn’t run to tell me,
you’d have fought until lunch break was over.
What’s wrong with your two clubs?
Why do you keep fighting?
This time,
I’m deducting your behavior points.
And you’ll have to complete
whatever activities you can
to make up for the points you lose.
Otherwise, you won’t graduate
from high school.
Damn.
It’s all your fault.
You started it.
No, you started it.
Who told you to extort money from people?
Did you not have your own?
I wasn’t bullying you, was I?
But he’s younger.
Please stop.
Let’s go.
Oh, please.
I thought they were tougher than that.
And you.
Why did you tell Suchart?
I was afraid to step in.
I was afraid I’d get caught in the middle.
Why would you step in?
I didn’t want you to get hurt.
I do judo.
You think I can’t fight them?
If I got hurt, I’d only hurt my hand
punching them in the face.
I know you can fight them,
but I don’t want you to get hurt.
Not even your hand.
My club has activities you can do
to earn points.
If you’re interested, come apply.
Mm. I’ll check it out.
Anyway, why do you keep
meddling in my business?
You call this meddling?
Oh?
You’re definitely meddling.
It’s not even your business.
I just wanted to help.
I didn’t mean to meddle.
Why would you help me?
You helped me yesterday.
Today, I wanted to help you too.
Is there anything else I can help you with?
Sea Clean.
P’Niran.
What?
Huh?
Hey.
How do you know my name?
Did you spy on me?
Ah.
I must be famous.
My name is Cheewa.
Or you can call me Parncheewa.
But Parncheewa is longer.
It’s up to you.
You can call me anything.
Then can I call you Glasses?
No.
My name is not Glasses.
Glasses are the object Parncheewa wears.
Right.
Gravity Junior.
If you want to use gravity on me again,
you can.
But I have to go to class now.
Once school’s over,
you can.
Huh?
Oh?
What’s wrong with him?
Leaving just like that.
P’Niran.
Please read the details in the brochure.
If you’re interested,
come to the Astronomy Club.
Top floor.
Science building.
I’m always there when I’m not in class.
Wait.
How would I know your timetable?
I can send it to you later.
You know Cheewa?
Are you guys close?
That kid with the glasses?
Hey.
I think they went that way.
Idiots.
Blind as hell.
You’re…
the guy who sat on my lap.
Don’t be ridiculous.
I didn’t want to sit on your lap.
Sorry.
You saved me. Thank you.
You’re pretty kind.
Gravity Senior.
My name is not Gravity.
Then what’s your name?
I’m not telling you.
You don’t need to know.
We’re not close.
I know the names of a lot of planets.
And I’m not close to any of them.
You’re just…
Ugh, never mind.
I don’t want to talk to you anymore.
Glasses.
Yes?
You should hurry home.
Or you’ll get your money taken again.
Hey.
Can you walk me out?
Huh?
What are you doing here, boys?
To…
Do you know
how old the universe is?
Once you learn more about something,
you’ll feel even closer to it.
Are you shy watching me change?
Why don’t you change in the restroom?
Can you walk me out?
Huh?
Are you out of your mind?
We’re not close.
We barely know each other.
And you want me to walk you out?
You’re crazy.
Just go.
They’re not following you anymore.
Go on ahead.
I’ll keep an eye out for you.
Go home.
Which way?
That way!
Do you want to follow them?
Aren’t you going to walk me out?
Seriously? Want me to throw you?
No.
Right.
Look at him.
Ugh.
What? Hurry up!
Left!
Did you see me talk to him?
Yeah.
Exactly. We’ve talked before.
What a dumb question.
No, I’m going that way!
Wanna get punched?
Are you sure, Niran?
It’s astronomy.
I only know Planet Namek.
I need to get my activity hours.
Otherwise, I won’t graduate with you guys.
Come on. Can’t you just join me?
What are you doing here, boys?
To… sign up for
the Astronomy Club’s Volunteer Camp.
Oh!
Welcome!
Great!
Come on in! Welcome!
You guys made the right choice.
Our club is happy to have you.
Are you into astronomy?
Did you know
that astronomy and the universe
are actually much closer to us than we think?
Closer to us?
Of course.
You may feel that it’s so vast and far away,
but actually, we’re part of it.
Do you know
how long it would take
to explore the universe?
No, I don’t.
Correct.
Oh?
I don’t know either.
That’s why we’re learning here.
Come on in.
We’re having fun.
Come on.
Oh, okay.
Hey, come greet our new friends.
I’ve been waiting for you.
See?
This one goes up like this.
Do people from outside the club
usually not join in?
Not really.
Do you know how old the universe is?
No.
Who would know?
Almost 14 billion years old.
Whoa.
14 thousand…
Zero.
Six.
Zeros.
Eight. Nine. Ten.
That’s one too many.
There are nine zeros.
It’s really old, huh?
Yes.
That’s why there are so many things
I want to know.
Are you into older people?
Maybe not that much older.
Once you learn more about something,
you’ll feel even closer to it.
Even closer.
And did you know
the stars we see might not exist
in the present?
It can take years for the light to reach us.
Or even millions of years.
What we see
might be from the past.
Stop it, Thara!
Your saliva is all over my shirt!
What the hell?
What?
Ew!
Why do you have a student shirt
in your bag?
And other shirts too.
I have everything in my bag.
Do you have mosquito repellent?
I have mosquito spray.
Just a second.
Stop. I’m just kidding.
Please go and change into my shirt.
You said you couldn’t stand
the smell of P’Thara’s saliva.
Why don’t you change in the restroom?
I’m just changing, not taking a shower.
Why?
Are you shy watching me change?
Hurry up.
Stop talking.
Just take off your glasses
if you don’t want to see.
No.
It’ll be hard for me to see.
It won’t be that hard.
Huh, Glasses?
How do you say it?
Just let gravity guide you.
Right?
Knowledge doesn't really sink in with you, does it?
Please hurry up and finish changing.
There’s no point in rambling.
I was listening to you ramble just now.
Fine.
So which one do you want?
This one.
No, I’m wearing it.
Take it off for me.
They’re the same.
Just wear that one.
Come here. Take it off.
So which one do you want?
That Cheewa kid is nice.
He even had a spare shirt for you to borrow.
Shut up. Wash my shirt.
Yeah. I’m going now.
See you.
Really? We live near each other?
That’s right.
Are you talking to me?
Yes.
Why didn’t you turn around to talk to me?
You didn’t seem like you wanted to talk to me on the bus.
So I pretended I didn’t see you.
It’s not like that.
It’s just…
I mean, we’re not close.
What do you want me to say?
Anything.
But…
I don’t even know
any of the planets you’re into.
I’m not just into planets.
Oh… really?
I’m into you, too.
Are you into anyone, P’Niran?
I want to get to know you better.
Can I hit on you?
Hold on.
It felt like the world stopped turning for a second.
Are you still worried about Auntie Tang?
Let’s come up with a plan
to win those customers back for her.
What are the seniors from the Music Club doing?
Whoever buys food from Auntie Tang today,
gets a free hug.
I’m here for a free hug.
You don’t have to do this.
No one’s forcing you.
I’m just claiming what I’m entitled to.
This means I’m another step closer
to winning you over, P’Niran.
Tell me honestly.
Aren’t you shy at all?
What’s wrong? Are you shy?
Why are you smiling so much?
Someday, you’ll smile at me like this.
After the match, I have a reward for you.
This is what happens when you miss practice.
No one deserves to be scolded for losing a sports competition, P’Niran.
Are you sad that you lost?
Of course.
I guess you won’t get to reward me, then.
I lost.
I was going to give you a gift anyway.